A Guide to the Papers of J. Warren White, Jr. 1970-1979
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Legislative Reference Material, 1971-1977
  - Regional Action, October, 1974 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Regional Action, April, 1976 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Regional White House Conference-Issue Papers (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Report of the Comptroller, 1975 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Reports of the Current Study Commission, 1974 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Report of the Treasurer of Virginia, 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Reports on Public Education in Virginia, 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Revenue Projections for Fiscal Years (General Fund), 1973-1976 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Review of General Assembly Action, 1975 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Revision of Certain Sections Appearing in Certain Chapters submitted with Interim Reports I and II (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Senate Document No. 16, 1974: Report of the Commission to study the Virginia Milk Commission (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Senate Document No. 38, 1975: Revision of Chapter 7 of Title 6 of the Virginia Code Commission (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Senate Document No. 39, 1975: Fifth Interim Report of The Commission on State Governmental Management (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Senate Document No. 40, 1975: Third Interim Report: Commission on State Governmental Management (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Senate Document No. 41, 1975: Fourth Interim Report of the Commission on State Governmental Management (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Senate Document No. 1, 1976: Address of Mills E. Godwin to the General Assembly, January 14, 1976 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Senate Document No. 3, 1976: Report on the Feasibility of Establishing a School of Optometry in Virginia (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Senate Document No. 4, 1976: Report to General Assembly As Directed by Senate Joint Resolution No. 147, 1975-made by the Division of Motor Vehicles (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Senate Document No. 6, 1976: Report on the Committee to Study the Education of Handicapped Children (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Senate Document No. 7, 1976: Report on the Commission on Human Resources Priorities (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Senate Document No. 8, 1976: Report on the Department of Welfare (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Senate Document No. 9, 1976: A Study of All Laws Pertaining to Compulsory School Attendance (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Senate Document No. 10, 1976: Report of the Department of Welfare (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Senate Document No. 12, 1976: Report of the Milk Commission-Study Commission (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Senate Document No. 29, 1976: Interim Reports of the Commission to study the Costs and Administration of Health Care Services (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Senate Document No. 4, 1977: Report of the Commission on the Acquisition of the Lorton Reformatory Complex (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Senate Document No. 18, 1977: Health Education in the Public Schools (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Service Integration for Deinstitutionalization (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Seventh Annual Evaluation Report: The Need-Education with a Marketable Skill, 1976 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Shell Reports: Enhanced Recovery, July 1975 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 20)
  - The SID (Service Integration for Deinstitutionalization) Report-Volume I, Summary, 1975 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Southern Legislative Conference: Summary of the Twenty-Ninth Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Staff Documents, Volume I: Executive Management Responsibilities, 1976 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 23)
  - State Actions in 1976 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 1)
  - State Consumer Action, Summary, 1974 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 2)
  - State Government: Focusing on the Legislatures, Summer, 1974 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 3)
  - State Government, Autumn, 1974 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 4)
  - State Government, Spring, 1975 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 5)
  - State Government, Summer, 1975 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 6)
  - State Government, Winter, 1975 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 7)
  - State Government, Spring, 1976 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 8)
  - State Government, Winter, 1976 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 9)
  - State Government News, August, 1976 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 10)
  - State Government News, September, 1976 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 11)
  - State Government News, October, 1976 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 12)
  - State Government News, November, 1976 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 13)
  - State of Virginia: The Law Governing the Examination, Licensure and Practice of Professional and Practical Nurses, 1974 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 14)
  - State Water Control Board; Memorandum, 1976 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Statewide Housing Needs Analysis, 1975 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Superintendent of Public Instruction: Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Teacher Aides, 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Tentative Allocation of Interstate, Primary and Urban Construction Funds, 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Tour: Governors Capital Outlay Budget, 1977 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 2)
  - US Railway Association's Preliminary System Plan, 1975 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 1)
  - USS Virginia: Commissioning, September 11, 1976 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Venue; Chapter 5 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Assessment/Sales, 1974 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Athletic Commission: Report to the Governor, 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Code Commission: Second Interim Report by T. Munford Boyd (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Code Commission: Third Interim Report by T. Munford Boyd (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Commission for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 1975 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1975 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Community College System, 1975 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Virginia: Department of Corrections: Comprehensive Action Plan, 1975-1984 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Department of Labor and Industry: Annual Report, 1975 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Department of Vocational Rehabilitation: Biennial Report, 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Department of Vocational Rehabilitation: Annual Report, 1976 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Virginia's Direction in Agency: A Timely Matter (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Education Association, 1975 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Election Laws as Amended to July 19, 1971 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Election Laws as Amended to April 5, 1975 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Government in Brief, 1975 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Higher Education: The 1976 General Assembly (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1974 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Journal of Education, April, 1975 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Virginia, Commonwealth: Opinions of the Attorney, 1974-1975 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Planning, 1974 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Virginia's Resources, 1975 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Virginia School Boards Association: Policies and Suggestions, 1976 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Virginia State Advisory council on Vocational Education: Fifth Annual Evaluation Report, 1974 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Virginia State Crime Commission: 19th Annual Report, 1974 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Virginia State Crime Commission: Annual Report, 1975 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Virginia: The Road to Independence, 1763-1783 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Water Law: An Economic Appraisal, 1976 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Wage Differentials for State Employees, 1975 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Where Virginia Ranks, 1976 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Will Higher Education be Ready for the Eighties?: Proceedings of the 25th SREB Legislative Work Conference, July 28-30, 1976 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Your Virginia State Government: Bicentennial Edition (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 9)
- Legislative Files, 1971-1979
  - Abortion, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Appreciation Notes for Campaign, 1971 and 1973 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Appropriations Committee I, 1977 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Appropriations Committee II, 1977 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Appropriations Committee III, 1977 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1979 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Arts and Humanities Commission, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Bills for 1979-General Assembly Session, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Campaign, 1971 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Campaign and Election Contributions and Expenditures, 1971 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Capital Outlay Program (Taxes), 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 11)
  - City of Norfolk, 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 12)
  - City of Norfolk, 1977 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 1)
  - City of Norfolk, 1979 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Coastal Resources Management Act-HB403, 1979 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Colleges and Universities, 1979 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Commissioner of Revenue Bills, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, General, 1978 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: One-Time Replies I, 1977 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: One-Time Replies II, 1977 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: One-Time Replies III, 1977 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Council of Higher Education, 1977-1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Credit Cards, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Laureate Awards, 1977 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Cumulative Index of Bills, Resolutions, Joint Resolutions, and Documents I, January 18, 1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Cumulative Index of Bills, Resolutions, Joint Resolutions, and Documents II, January 18, 1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Cumulative Index of Bills, Resolutions, Joint Resolutions, and Documents I, January 31, 1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Cumulative Index of Bills, Resolutions, Joint Resolutions, and Documents II, January 31, 1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Cumulative Index of Bills, Resolutions, Joint Resolutions, and Documents III, January 31, 1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Advisory Committee Report of the State Party, 1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Directories, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Education-Correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Education, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Election Laws, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Opposition, 1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Support, 1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Equality Yes! ERA No !! (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 1)
  - ERA I, 1978 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 2)
  - ERA II, 1978 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 3)
  - ERA III, 1978 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 4)
  - ERA IV, 1978 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 5)
  - ERA V, 1978 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 6)
  - ERA VI, 1978 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 7)
  - ERA, 1979 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Gas, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Hampton Roads Area Committee, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Index of the Opinions of the Attorney General of Virginia, 1967-1977 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Interim Reports, 1978 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1979 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Joint Rules Committee, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Judges, 1979 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Packages, 1977-1979 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Letters from Chuck Robb, 1979 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Mail, 1979 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Mary Baldwin College, 1976-1978 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Mini Journal/Weekly, Daily, 1979 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Bills-Support/Oppose I, 1977 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Bills-Support/Oppose II, 1977 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Bills, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Mr. White's Bills, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Non-District ERA Opposition I, 1978 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Non-District ERA Opposition II, 1978 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Non-District ERA Support I, 1978 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Non-District ERA Support II, 1978 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Non-District ERA Support III, 1978 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Non-District ERA Support IV, 1978 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Non-District ERA Support, 1979 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Norfolk General I, 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Norfolk General II, 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Norfolk General III, 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk Sheriff, 1975-1977 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Old Dominion University, 1979 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Optometrist Bill, 1979 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Ports-General Assembly Session, 1979 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Privileges and Elections, 1976-1977 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Privileges and Elections I, 1978 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Privileges and Elections II, 1978 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Privileges and Elections I, 1979 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Privileges and Elections II, 1979 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Public Hearings-ERA, 1978 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaires and Newsletters, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Bill, 1976 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Speeches, 1975-1977 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 3)
  - State Sales Tax, 1977 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Taxes, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 5)
  - The Washington, D.C., Amendment, 1979 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 6)
  - To Do, 1979 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 7)
  - VALC Arts and Humanities I, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 1)
  - VALC Arts and Humanities II, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 2)
  - VALC Arts and Humanities III, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 3)
  - VALC Arts and Humanities IV, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Vending Machines-Sales Department, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Veterans, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Port Authority, August 25, 1977 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Port Authority-Correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Port Authority-Minutes, 1977 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Port Authority-Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Port Authority-Newspaper Clippings, 1977 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 5)
  - VSRS-Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 6)